

# Stefanija Stanković

web design engineer

I am a designer and front-end developer specialised in creating beautiful marketing material and developing web templates. I have the ability to work within a team as well as cross-team and I love to work with customers. They offer me guidelines and I give artistic and unique shapes to their visions. I also help businesses, organisations and individuals design modern, interesting interfaces and define meaningful experiences for web and mobile applications. I am a very passionate designer that is always waiting to grow, learn and try something new. I love what I do and I work exceptionally hard, no matter who I work with.

In my spare time, I enjoy playing computer games and taking long walks with my boyfriend and our dog. I also love reading, drawing and cycling, and I love doing yoga to relax at the end of a long day. I am spending a couple of hours every evening searching for new trends in design and web technologies. I also enjoy cooking, especially baking - it helps me in learning to focus on detailed instructions and procedures, since this is very important in my line of work. Eating fresh and healthy food also helps me to relax and stay healthy.

# SOFTWARE SKILLS

























51 Klarenbeekstraat, Haarlem, Netherlands

stefanijadesign@gmail.com

www.stefaniadesign.com

## **EDUCATION**

The Higher Education Technical School 2009-2015. • of Professional Studies

Bachelor degree in graphic engineering and design web design

Technical school "Mileva 2004-2008. Marić-Ajnstajn"

Graphic technician.

### **EXPERIENCES**

2016-2018 • "Dynamicsoft" software company

My position was a UI/UX designer and a front-end developer. As a part of a team, I was worked on maintaining WSC Printer, which is the CMS software solution for the printing industry. I specialised in designing and developing nice e-commerce themes. For the design process, I use Adobe Experience, InVision, Photoshop, Illustrator and for the theme development, I work with HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap and Angular2.

"Execom" software engineering 2015-2016 company

I worked on a freelance designer position for 6 months in a team consisting of both programmers and marketing experts. We worked on a campaign for the "KONTEH" fair. I was designing UI for a game/quiz web app for new employees, a logo and other marketing material for that fair. Also, I was hired for the Android Hackathon event and designed promo marketing materials such as posters. T-Shirts. stickers, flyers, etc.

"Creative Tree" web design studio 2013-2014

I finished a 3 month internship in this company. I had the opportunity to design web mockups for the clients. Also, I made progress working in CMS, especially Wordpress, so I learned a lot about designing and developing Wordpress themes.

Freelance 2012-Present

> I am designing promo marketing materials, logos, banners, websites, etc.

"Futura" printing office 2009-2010.

I was working there as a graphic designer for about 6 months. I learned a lot about graphic preparation for printing and started to be more confident working with softwares, such as Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Indesign and CorelDRAW.